#### Contact

luccaaugusto@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/luccaugusto (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Programação orientada a objetos (POO)

**MySQL** 

Automação

# Lucca Augusto Santos

Software Engineer - I bring your ideas to life

Belo Horizonte, Minas Gerais, Brazil

### Summary

About being a computer scientist: Free Software and Linux advocate, I believe computers and technology are here to allow humans to experience a better life and not have to worry about repetitive, mind numbing types of work and allowing us to focus on what really makes us live, but there's a long way until we get there, until then we must try to have a healthy relationship with technology.

About not being a programmer: I like to explore my creative side by doing illustration, skating and all sorts of creative work, i'm always trying something new.

## Experience

City Shoppe

Desenvolvedor full stack
June 2021 - January 2023 (1 year 8 months)

Development of a wordpress plugin to host the CityShoppe plataform Development of a NodeJS Shopify app to connect to the wordpress marketplace

Development of a new marketing product and platform in NestJS and NodeJS Migration from the Wordpress platform to the new one, using AWS

Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Minas Gerais Compiler Discipline Monitor February 2021 - June 2021 (5 months)

Belo Horizonte, Minas Gerais, Brasil

Educando Seu Bolso
Desenvolvedor da web
August 2019 - August 2020 (1 year 1 month)
Belo Horizonte, Minas Gerais, Brasil

Focus on developing the front-end in ReactJS and the back-end in Python (Django)

Educando Seu Bolso Desenvolvedor da web August 2017 - January 2019 (1 year 6 months) Belo Horizonte, Minas Gerais, Brasil

Basic experience with SEO.

Back-end development in PHP (Wordpress) and Python (Django). Front-end development in ReactJS and pure HTML.

#### Education

Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Minas Gerais Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)